Are you okay?
大丈夫?
I haven't put my finger in it yet.
まだ指入れてないんだよ
I was pretty bored
結構ペンカンになってた
Yo.
よ
Girl don't want to sit down?
女 の子座りしたくない?
O-kun, aren't you in pain?
おうくん、苦しくないの?
Yeah.
うん
I'm feeling full.
ぷんぷんしてる
I'm scared.
こわいって
How far can it go?
どこまで入る?
In your mouth.
口の中
Yeah.
うん
I'm scared.
こわいって
Yeah.
うん
Were you made to practice?
練習させられたの?
Yeah.
うん
why?
なんで?
Can you do it?
できるの?
that.
それ
up to the throat.
喉のところまで
painful.
苦しい
Your throat is amazing.
喉、すごいね
That's on purpose.
わざそれ
Yeah.
うん
That's amazing.
すごいね
Feels good.
気持ちいい
Really.
めっちゃ
Yeah.
うん
I feel like sleeping.
寝たくなってきちゃった
Yeah.
うん
I can stand it.
我慢できる
Go to sleep.
寝てこい
Can I just put it in like this?
このまま入れていい?
Yeah.
うん
Let me sleep and it feels good.
寝るようにならせて、気持ちいい
Yeah.
うん
It's really tight.
すごい締まるね
Mom feels better.
ママの方が気持ちいいね
The face.
顔ね
It's pretty easy to get around.
結構、いきやすいね
It's soaking wet.
びちょびちょだもんね
We were talking quite well until just now,
さっきまで結構よくしゃべってたのに、
Why do you say such bad things?
なんでこんな悪口になるの?
Yeah.
うん
Because it hurts so bad.
めっちゃ痛いから
It's crazy.
めっちゃだよ
Yeah.
うん
Does it feel good?
気持ちいいの?
I want to switch it up one day.
なんか一日、スイッチしたいね
It's tight.
締まるね
Sleep properly.
ちゃんと寝て
Yes, show me.
はい、見せて
Goyacchi.
ごやっち
sleep?
寝る?
It looks like my dick is being eaten.
ちんちゃん食べられちゃってるみたい
I fell asleep.
寝ちゃった
I cried because I couldn't sleep well.
なかなか寝るのから泣けちゃった
Do you understand?
わかる?
This is so wet.
このびちょびちょ
I've got everything.
全部取れてるよ
sorry.
ごめんなさい
It feels so good.
こんな気持ちいい
Let me tell you with my feet.
足で申し上げてもらおう
Did you know you ate it?
食べたの分かった?
My butt is warm.
お尻が温かい
warm?
温かい?
I almost cried when I finished it.
仕上がって泣かそっか
Yeah.
うん